to laugh.
Like I said, welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer where we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep. Brother James.
Yes, sir. And God spake all these words,
saying, I am the Lord thy God, which
have brought thee out of the land of
Egypt, out of the house of bondage. Thou
shalt have no other gods before me. Thou
shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in the
earth beneath, or that is in the water
under the earth. Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I
the Lord thy God am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy. Sixth day shalt thou labor
and do all thy work. But the seventh day
is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In
it thou shalt not do any work. Thou nor
thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in them is, and rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hollowed it. Honor thy father
and thy mother, that thy days may be
long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee. Thou shalt not kill.
Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou
shalt not steal. Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor. Thou
shalt not covet thy neighbor's house.
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's
wife, nor as man's servant, nor as maid
servant, nor as ox, nor as ass, nor
anything that is thy neighbors. I read
Exodus 20:es 1-17. May the Lord add a
blessing to the reading of this word. In
Jesus name we pray. Amen. Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time. The questions we
will not answer are the vague and the
long scripture questions as well as
questions of debate. We are not here to
debate. We are here to spread the true
gospel of Jesus. So please be as direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible. No
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program. Also, keep
in mind that this is a live stream. So,
feel free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life. We just ask
that you keep your questions to a two
scripture maximum. But let me introduce
to you the family that's on the panel
this evening. Brother Dre, good evening.
Brother Jerome, grace and peace. Brother
Julius, good evening everybody. Brother
James, good evening everyone. Sister
Deborah, good evening. And we have
Sister Casey with us as well as a guest
caller. And I'm brother Cornell. Sister
Deborah, what is our first question of
the evening? Yes, there are several
heldover questions that will be answered
first before getting into tonight's Q&A.
Melon Natural Journey asks, "Are
dinosaurs mentioned anywhere in the
Bible?"
Dinosaurs,
are they mentioned anywhere in the
Bible, Brother Julius?
No,
they're not. They're not mentioned
anywhere in the Bible because that was
not for our creation.
Let's go let's go to second Peter the
third chapter.
Let me show you what I'm talking about
and why we say what they're not
mentioned.
Second Peter the third chapter, brother
James, we going to read verses 5 and
six.
Okay.
For this they willingly are ignorant of
that by the word of God the heavens were
of old and the earth standing out of the
water and in the water. Out of the water
and in the water. That's why Genesis the
first chapter tell you that the dry land
appear. He brought the earth out of the
water. Continue in verse six. Whereby
the world that then was being overflowed
with water perished. So now what world
perished? The world of the dinosaurs. We
know that they were here because we have
their fossils. That's where we get our
coal, our oil, and our natural gas from
dead trees, plants, and animals. It's
the same thing as us. The same thing
that they ate is in us. So therefore,
but that was for the Lord used those
animals because he knew this man had to
eat and had to keep warm. So therefore,
he prepared the earth for mankind.
So therefore now the world, he's going
to fix the world for spirit beings.
Sisters and brothers, it's not hard to
understand. So the word dinosaurs is not
in the Bible because it does not pertain
to our creation. That's all I got on
that.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
Hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next question. Moving on.
Most love asks in Job 9 verse 24.
What does it mean? The earth is given
into the hand of the wicked.
Well, we see a lot of signs of that
today when you consider what's going on
all around this world. It's a lot of
wicked everywhere. But let's go in there
Job 9. Let's go into Job the 9th
chapter.
So, when you get there, brother, Job 9,
and let's pick it up. Um, read verse 22
and then skip down to 24. Okay.
This is one thing, therefore I said it.
He destroyth the perfect and the wicked.
Yep. So, those is doing it right as well
as those that's doing wrong. Lord, don't
have no respect to person. Verse 24. The
earth is given into the hand of the
wicked. He coverereth the faces of the
judges thereof. If not, where? And who
is he? Yep. It say the earth is given
unto the hand of the wicked. So, let's
uh turn back. Let's see where it all got
started. Let's go back Genesis the third
chapter.
And let's pick it up.
Let's read that verse two and three.
Okay. Genesis 3 2 and 3. Go ahead,
brother. And the woman said unto the
serpent, "We may eat of the fruit of the
trees of the garden, but of the fruit of
the tree which is in the midst of the
garden, God has said, Ye shall not eat
of it, neither shall ye touch it, least
ye die." Skip down to verse six.
And when the woman saw that the tree was
good for food, and that it was pleasant
to the eyes, and a tree to be desired to
make one wise, she took of the fruit
thereof, and did eat, and gave also unto
her husband with her, and he did eat.
Not an apple, but the words of Satan is
what they ate right there. And that
started to put things in motion. Eve ate
it first and then went and took it to
her husband and he did eat. And skip
down to verse 10 and 11. Go ahead. And
he said, "I heard thy voice in the
garden and I was afraid because I was
naked and I hid myself." So this is Adam
here saying he heard the voice of the
Lord. He was afraid and naked. He didn't
know what nakedness was until Satan
talked to him. What the Lord say in
verse 11? And he said, "Who told thee
that thou was naked? Hast thou eaten of
the tree whereof I commanded thee that
thou shouldest not eat?" Skip down to
verse 17 and go ahead. And unto Adam he
said, Because thou has hearkened unto
the voice of thy wife, and has eaten of
the tree of which I commanded thee,
saying, Thou shalt not eat of it, cursed
is the ground for thy sake. and sorrow
shalt thou eat of it all the days of thy
life. So this thou to set the wickedness
in motion right here, even death. Go
ahead.
Thorns also, and thistles shall it bring
forth to thee, and thou shalt eat of the
herb of the field.
And the sweat of thy face shall thou eat
bread, till thou return unto the ground,
for out of it was thou taken. For dust
thou art, and unto dust shalt thou
return. It was man that brought death
onto the table, but God is the one that
created and orchestrated it because he
never intended for it to be. But as far
as you asking about the world given over
into the hand of the wicked, let's turn
over to Jeremiah 8. This will be my last
place. Jeremiah 8.
Because this is going on even until this
day. Just take a good look around. You
see, wickedness is everywhere from one
end of the earth clean unto the other.
And why is that, brother James? Read
that. Jeremiah 8 and3. Go ahead.
And death shall be chosen rather than
life by all the residue of them that
remain of this evil family, which remain
in all the places whether I have driven
them, saith the Lord of hosts. So if you
got death being chosen rather than life,
you got wickedness everywhere without
end until the Lord comes and end it. But
uh that's all I got. Anybody else want
to add?
All right, we hope that answered your
question there. That's why we have all
this wickedness going on. Let us move on
to our next question, sister.
Uh yes and it's from Sister Audrey B
asks, "Where can we read that the
dietary laws are still in effect?"
Brother Dre, we know the dietary law
still in effect, but where can we go and
read that, brother? Shed some light. You
can read in Leviticus 11 about the
dietary law that God put in effect and
it never changed. Before that, you had
the clean and the unclean.
It It's been there. But let's look at
something about Peter who was an apostle
of Jesus.
Let's see what he said when these
unclean animals came down on the plate
for him. Surely he would know if it was
done away. I think the bigger question
should be asks of the people that think
it's not in effect. When did it become
not in effect?
And when did God say you can eat
whatever you want to? Never.
But let we going to look at a couple of
things. Uh Acts 10 and I want you to uh
pick it up at verse 10 because there was
this plate came down and Peter being
prepared to deal with Cornelius. He was
hungry. He prayed and this plate came
down. He fell into a trance. Verse 10.
Go ahead. And he became very hungry and
would have eaten. But while they made
ready, he fell into a trance. Mhm. Go
ahead. And saw heaven open, and a
certain vessel descending unto him, as
it had been a great sheet knit at the
four corners, and let down to the earth.
Mhm. Go ahead. where wherein were all
manner of 4-footed beasts of the earth
and wild beasts and creeping things and
fowls of the air. Go ahead. And there
came a voice to him, "Rise, Peter, and
eat." What did Peter say? Go ahead. But
Peter said, "Not so, Lord, for I have
never eaten anything that is common or
unclean." Peter said, "Not so. I have
never eaten anything common or unclean.
So was now cleansed.
Peter would have said, "Okay, pass me
that whatever that 4-footed beast was."
But he didn't say that. But what was
this about? Skip down to verse 28 and
read it.
And he said unto them, "Ye know how that
it is a an unlawful thing for a man that
is a Jew to keep company or come unto
one of another nation." But God has
showed me that I should not call any man
common or unclean. Not to call any man
common or unclean. The beasts were just
used to prepare Peter to understand who
he was going to be dealing with,
Cornelius. Now, I want to look at at the
coming of the Lord. Let's go to 2
Thessalonians the first chapter. 2
Thessalonians, the first chapter. And I
want to pick it up at verse 7. When you
get there, go ahead, brother.
And to you who are troubled, rest with
us. When the Lord Jesus shall be
revealed from heaven with his all with
his mighty angels
in flaming fire, taking vengeance on
them that know not God and that obey not
the gospel of our Lord Jesus Christ. Go
ahead. Who shall be punished with
everlasting destruction from the
presence of the Lord and from the glory
of his power. But we talking about the
coming of the Lord when he is going to
come with vengeance, taking vengeance on
them that know not God and obey not the
gospel of our Lord Jesus Christ. He is
coming one time. Let's go look at that
one time, one more time in Isaiah 66 and
pick it up at verse 15. This is the last
scripture. Isaiah 66 15-1 17. Go ahead,
brother.
Okay. For behold, the Lord will come
with fire and with his chariots like a
whirlwind to render his anger with fury
and his rebuke with flames of fire. This
is talking about the same coming of the
Lord.
So we talking about is it all right to
eat anything unclean. Go ahead. For by
fire and by his sword will the Lord
plead with all flesh, and the slain of
the Lord shall be many. Go ahead. They
that sanctify themselves and purify
themselves in the gardens behind one
tree in the midst, eating swine's flesh,
and the abomination, and the mouse shall
be consumed together, sayeth the Lord.
Those that sanctify themselves and
purify themselves behind the gardens in
the midst eating swine's flesh and the
abomination and the mouse which are
unclean things will be consumed together
saith the Lord. This is what the Lord is
saying and this is at the coming of the
Lord. So, the dietary law is still in
effect.
I hope that helped.
Yes, sir. Brother Dre, like you said in
that Leviticus 11, Lord said, "This is
the law to make a difference between the
beast she shall eat and the beast she
shall not eat." Still good for today,
ain't it, brother? That is right,
brother. Yes, sir. Thank you for that
light. As we continue to move on to our
next question, moving on. Michelle Cliss
wants understanding
on Exodus 34 verse 26.
Exodus 34 and 26. Why don't we go there,
brother James, and then the guest
caller, we'll take it from there.
Okay. Exodus 34:26 says, "The first of
the first fruits of thy land, thou shalt
bring unto the house of the Lord thy
God. Thou shalt not see the kid in his
mother's milk.
Well, the first thing is the Lord is
letting you know that the uh
when you uh uh reap anything, whether
it's money or whether fruit or anything
else, he want heals off the top before
you take anything. Let's go to Leviticus
the 23rd chapter and we're going to read
verse 10. And then we're going to skip
down and read verse 14.
Okay. Leviticus 23 verse 10 says, "Speak
unto the children of Israel, and say
unto them, when ye become into the land
which I give unto you, and shall reap
the harvest thereof, then ye shall bring
a sheath of the first fruits of your
harvest unto the priest."
Verse Mhm.
Go ahead. Verse 14 says, "And ye shall
eat neither bread nor parched corn nor
green ears until the selfsame day that
ye have brought an offering unto your
God. It shall be a statute forever
throughout your generations and all your
dwellings."
So if you grow food fruit or you grow
whatever you grow out of the ground or
whatever your increase is. So you
supposed to go and offer the Lord his
first right off the top before you eat
anything. It's just like when you uh
when you get paid first money out of
your check is be supposed to be set
aside right off the top. God's 10%
tithe. All he's saying is
before you eat anything or before you
spend anything, I want mine first.
That's why he say you don't eat no bread
or parched corn or anything until you
have made an offering to the Lord. And
the second part is that don't uh uh uh
uh uh
what is that seat a lamb a uh uh the kid
in his mother's milk? I really don't
know what that mean but a kid is called
a baby goat. So we could be saying don't
get a baby goat and boil in his mother's
milk. But truth but the truth of the
matter is I don't know what that mean.
All right. All I have to say about that.
All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
Next one. Palmer, Alaska says, "So when
Jesus was crucified,
was he killed in the years 3500,
mist of the week?"
So when Jesus was crucified, was he
killed in the year 3500,
mist of the week? Guess caller.
Jesus was killed in 30
AD.
April uh uh April uh uh the 5th which is
Abel the 14th on a Wednesday.
That's what history tells. That's what
history has it that he was crucified on
a Wednesday, April the 5th, which is the
14th day of Abel in 30 AD.
That's all I have to say. All right.
Hope that answered your question there
as we continue to move on. Moving on.
Dora Walder asks in Joshua 53-15.
Who is this man? Because Deuteronomy
34:10
says, "And there arose not a prophet
since in Israel like unto Moses who the
Lord knew face to face."
All right, brother Jerome. Two
scriptures are given here.
Go ahead, my brother.
Oh, you're on mute, brother Jerome.
Thank you. Let's go read it. Uh Joshua
the 5th chapter verse 13-15.
Okay. It says, "And it came to pass when
Joshua was by Jericho that he lifted up
his eyes and looked and behold there
stood a man over against him with his
sword drawn in his hand. And Joshua went
unto him and said unto him, "Art thou
for us or for our adversaries?"
And he said, "Nay, but as captain of the
host of the Lord am I now come." And
Joshua fell on his face to the earth,
and did worship, and said unto him,
"What saith my Lord unto his servant?"
And the captain of the Lord's host said
unto Joshua, "Loose thy shoe from off
thy foot, for the place where on thou
standeth is holy." And Joshua did so.
Okay. Um and let's go read the
um Deuteronomy 34 and 10. Okay. that
says, "And there arose not a prophet
since Israel like unto Moses whom the
Lord knew face to face."
Okay. Now, these are two different
things. They're not related. Okay? Uh
now in that Joshua 15, that man was
actually Michael, the archangel. He's
the captain of the Lord's host. Talking
about the host, all the hosts of the
holy angels. Okay. So, let's go to
Psalms 148 and reverse two and we going
to tie it with Revelations.
Psalms 148.
And you said verse two. Yeah, just verse
two.
Praise ye him all his angels. Praise ye
him all his host. And the host here are
the angels. Okay. So now let's tie this
with Revelations
12 and read verse 7. Okay. Revelation 12
verse 7 says,
"And there was war in heaven. Michael
and his angels fought against the
dragon. and the dragon fought and his
angels.
Yeah. So, Archangel Michael was the one
that was talking to him in that Joshua
3. Okay. Now, regarding that Deuteronomy
34 and 10, that's not associated with
that Joshua 3 at all. It's talking about
Moses. Okay? That's who it's talking
about. And he was just saying ain't no
prophet out there,
you know, in relationship to who he was
referring to. And that was talking about
Moses. Nobody else. Okay, that's all I
got on you.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question. Yes.
Next question. Pauline R asked you to
explain what Luke 16 verse9 means.
She says, "I read the verses seven and
8, but I want to know what the Lord is
saying in verse 9."
All right. They want some explanation on
Luke 16 and9. James, let's go there.
Okay.
And then they
seven and eight.
But go ahead, brother. And the guest
caller would take it from there. Okay.
Luke 16:E9 says, "And I say unto you,
make to yourselves friends of the mammon
of unrighteousness, that when ye fail,
that they may receive you into
everlasting habitations."
Okay. The first thing is let's see uh uh
uh what precede that back up to verse
one and read.
Verse one says, "And he said also unto
his disciples, there was a certain rich
man which had a steward, and the same
was accused unto him that he had wasted
his goods."
Go ahead. And he called him and said
unto him, "How is it that I hear this of
thee? Give an account of thy
stewardship, for thou mayest be no
longer steward."
Okay. For now, he heard something of me.
He said, "Look, you ain't going to be no
longer a steward because of your
behavior." Let's get see what this guy
did. Go ahead.
Then the steward said within himself,
"What shall I do? For my Lord taketh
away from me the stewardship I cannot
dig to beg I am ashamed
I am resolved what to do that when I am
put out of the stewardship they may
receive me in their houses
so he called every one of his lord's
debtors unto him and said unto the first
how much owest thou unto my lord Lord,
and he and he said 100 measures of oil.
And he said unto him, "Take thy bill,
and sit down quickly, and write 50."
Then said he Then said he to another,
"And how much owest thou?" And he said,
"1 measures of wheat." And he said unto
him, "Take thy bill and write four
score."
Go ahead. And the Lord commanded the
unjust steward com commanded the unjust
steward because he had done wisely for
the children of the world are in their
generation wiser than the children of
light.
Okay.
He recommended he commended this guy
because uh he went and uh uh recovered
finances from his friend
because he had already lost his
stewardship. And look at what the Lord
said about this guy. He said, you know,
the Lord uh commended him
and they'll just do it because he had
done wisely for the children of this
world in this generation is wiser than
the children of light. So if he's the
children of the world and he's not the
children of light, that means that uh he
ain't serving God no more.
So the Lord is telling them to do what?
Reading. Now read verse N. And I say
unto you, make to yourselves friends of
the mammon of unrighteousness,
that when ye fail, they may receive you
into everlasting habitations.
Well, I don't know how long this
habitation going to be, but he's telling
you you may as well go ahead and make
you friends of mammoth, friends of the
world, because uh you didn't serve me.
You ain't got nothing coming in the
future.
Now, skip right down and read verses 11
through 13. Okay. It says, "If therefore
ye have not been faithful in the
unrighteous mammon, who will commit to
your trust the true wi rich riches? And
if ye have not been faithful in that
which is another man's, who shall give
you that which is your own? No servant
can serve two masters. Either he will
hate the one and love the other, or else
he will hold on to the hold to the one
and despise the other. Ye cannot serve
God and mammon.
Now what he's really saying here is if
you going to serve God, you got to walk
in his ways. But if you going to serve
the world like this steward did unwind,
you know, then go on out there and make
friends with the world. Get all the
money you can. enjoy all of the sin you
can because uh you will not get in the
kingdom of God cuz you cannot serve God
and money. You cannot serve God and also
the devil.
It's just like Paul said, you know, it's
uh the Gentiles sacrifice the devils.
As Gentiles sacrifice the devil, then
you cannot, he said, you cannot sit at
the Lord's table and sit at the devil's
table also. That's why Adam and Eve got
kicked out to God because they sat down
at Satan's table. Yeah. So simply the
Lord is simply saying is
you wise in the world, go out and live
the best you can, get all the money you
can, do whatever you want to do because
you will not get into the good side of
the kingdom. You going to the lake of
fire.
Simple as that. Wow.
What does it profit a man to gain the
whole world and lose his soul? That's
what it comes down to. Yep.
All right. We hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next
next question. Deborah Wilder says, "I
was wondering
uh in Joshua 5 verse 15, is it a reason
why Joshua was asked to loose thy shoe
from off thy foot? For the place where
on thou standest is holy." Does this
mean something symbolic?
Definitely got a meaning, brother
Julius.
Julius, you're on mute.
It means uh we're going to do something
real easy. We're going to read exactly
what it says. He gives you the answer.
And the answer is really simple. Let's
go to Joshua. Sometime we want to read
more into this and it's nothing more
into it than just obey.
Joshua 5 and verse 15. Read it. And the
captain of the Lord's host said unto
Joshua, "Loose thy shoe from off thy
foot, for the pl for the place whereon
thou standest is holy." And
Joshua did so. Let's go to Exodus the
third chapter.
Exodus the third chapter.
And this is in the days of Moses.
Pick it up at verse
five.
And he said, "Draw not nigh hither. Put
off thy shoes from off thy feet. For the
place for the place whereon thou
standest is holy ground." And Moses did
so. Last place. Acts chapter 7.
Acts chapter 7, read 31 and then read
33. Okay. Acts 7 and31 says, "When Moses
saw it, he wondered at the sight, and as
he drew near to behold it, the voice of
the Lord came unto him."
Skip down to verse 33. This is the angel
speaking out of the bush. Go ahead.
Then said the Lord to him, "Put off thy
shoes from thy feet for the for the
place where thou standest is holy
ground." So we can't read no more after
that. It just tells you take off your
shoes from off your feet for the ground
that you stand on is holy and you obey.
We can't add to it because there's no
nothing else written about it. That's
all I got, Cornell.
All right,
thank you for that. Hope that answered
any question as we move on with the time
check. Uh, yes, the time is 806.
Trisha would like an explanation on
Ezekiel 16
2-5.
Ezekiel 16:es 2-5.
Brother Jerome,
let's go read it. Okay.
When you get it, go ahead.
Son of man, cause Jerusalem to know her
abominations,
and say, "Thus sayeth the Lord God unto
Jerusalem, thy birth, and thy nativity
is of the land of Canaan. Thy father was
an Amorite, and thy mother an Hitittite.
and asked for thy nativity. In the day
that thou was born, thy navl was not
cut, neither was thou washed in water to
supplee. Thou was not salted at all, nor
swaddled at all. None I pied thee to do
any of these unto thee to have
compassion upon thee, but thou was cast
out in the open field to the loathing of
thy person in the day that thou was
born.
Okay. And that's talking about when it
said Jerusalem right there and it was u
three tribes in Jerusalem. So you had um
Benjamin, Judah, and um Levi. And so but
they Israelites. They are part of the 12
tribes. Okay. and the nativity of the
nation of Israel when it mentions uh the
Amorites and the Hittites,
they were the people of the land of
Canaan, which is the land the Lord gave
to the children of Israel. So that was
the that was the land of their nativity,
the land of Canaan. Okay. Now, uh, as
far as the verse four through five,
uh, it talked about, uh, can you read
that four and five? That four for me?
Read that four for me again. And as for
thy nativity, in the day that thou was
born, thy navl was not cut. Neither was
thou washed in water to supplee. Thou
was not salted at all, nor swaddled at
all. Yeah. And so be before the Lord uh
came before him to get them ready to be
his people, he's saying these negative
things about them. They they weren't
clean. They didn't had the Lord's word.
Okay? And that's what clean us up.
That's what salt us, right? So I wanted
to show you a verse about that. Salted.
Let's go to u Matthews chapter 5 and
read verse 13. And he said they wasn't
salted.
Okay. And hold that. Yeah. Hold that 16
Ezekiel. We going to come back. Okay.
Matthew 5 and13 says, "Ye are the salt
of the earth. But if the salt have lost
its savor, wherewith shall it be
salted?" It is thenforth good for
nothing, but to be cast out, and to be
trotten underfoot of men. Yeah. And
that's pretty much applied to this
nation here, Israel, the children of
Israel. Before the Lord came, that
applied to them. They wasn't salted.
Okay. So, verse go back to that uh
Ezekiel 15 and read that five for me.
Okay. 16. Yeah. Uh 16 and five. 16.
Yeah. And five. Okay.
None I pity thee to do any of these unto
thee, to have com compassion upon thee,
but thou was cast out in the open field
to the loathing of thy person in the day
that thou was born. Yeah. But then the
Lord,
he got him. Clean them up. Okay. So,
that's all I got on that. Uh, anybody
want to add something?
All right. Thank the Lord for that pity
he showed them people in that Ezekiel 16
brother. All right. As we move on to our
next question. Next question. Edward
Bobber asks, "When Jesus returns to
reather Israel, will they have a chance
to repent and turn from being wicked or
not?"
He's certainly going to return. Dre.
what you say. Let's go to uh Ezekiel the
20th chapter. Ezekiel 20 and we're going
to pick it up at verse 34. Ezekiel 20
and34.
Okay.
Go ahead, brother.
and I will bring you out from the people
and will gather you out of the countries
wherein ye are scattered with a mighty
hand and with a stretched out arm and
with fury poured out. Now I want to read
that verse 33 because we want to know
that the Lord is going to gather us but
he is going to rule over us. Go ahead.
As I live, sayeth the Lord God, surely
with a mighty hand, and with a stretched
out arm, and with fury poured out will I
rule over you. Now, skip down to verse
35. Go ahead. And I will bring you into
the wilderness of the people, and there
will I plead with you face to face. Go
ahead. Like as I pleaded with your
fathers in the wilderness of the land of
Egypt, so will I plead with you, saith
the Lord God. Go ahead. And I will cause
you to pass under the rod, and I will
bring you into the bond of the covenant,
and I will purge out from among you the
rebels, and them that transgress against
me. I will bring them forth out of the
country where they sjjoin, and they
shall not enter into the land of Israel,
and ye shall know that I am the Lord."
Verse 38 says, "He is going to bring you
into the wilderness, and he is going to
purge out from among us the rebellious."
So, this is your last time. If you get
in there and you rebellious,
you will get purged out and you will not
enter into the land of Israel.
But you have an opportunity to get it
right.
And this is it.
And even right now, we need to be
getting it right. But here, this
scripture speaks to your question.
Yes. Yes.
Get it right. That's all I got. Yes,
sir.
You hear that word, harden not your
heart, Brother Dre. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Thank you for that. As we move on to our
next question. Next question. Jeffrey
Meyers asks, "Who are the Asian
descendants of?" In other words, which
son of Noah. All right, Julius. Who are
the Asians descendants of? And which one
of sons of Noah did he come out of? They
came out of Noah's son Jester
or what you call the gentile. Let's go
to Genesis chapter 10. We're going to
read 1 to5.
Okay. The word Asia just means east.
You have
central. You have western Europe,
Central Europe and Eastern Europe which
is called Asia. Some people call it Asia
Minor, but the bottom line is east means
Asia means east. When you get it,
verse one, go ahead. Now, these are the
generations of the sons of Noah, Shim,
Ham, and Japheth. And unto them were
sons born after the flood. Go ahead. The
sons of Japth, Goomer and Magog, and
Maidi, and Jan, and Tubal, and Mach and
Tyrus.
And the sons of Goomemer, Ashkanaz, and
Rifath, and Toggamoth, and the sons of
Javan, Elishot, and Tarses, Hdum, and
Dodin. Uh-huh. By these were the aisles
of the Gentiles divided in their lands,
everyone after his tongue, after their
families and their nations. Now, some
people says that the Asians
are descendants of Ham. I can't see that
because all Ham's children are black.
But you have Gentiles and you have gent
uh you have Gentiles who are different
shades of white.
Mhm. And you have Gentiles who have
slanted eyes.
Some have skinny noses, some have wide
noses, some have thick lips, some have
thin lips, some have round faces, and
then some have different types of faces,
but they are different uh shades of
white. We call the Chinese man the
yellow man, but the bottom line is they
still are different shades of white
because God made them that way. So
therefore the Asians are descendants of
uh Noah's son Japth and they are all
grouped together
mostly Eastern Europe. JFest children
they have all of Europe but the Asians
occupy uh h the uh uh Eastern Europe but
they all are Europeans. They they just
east. That's all that's all I got.
Anybody want to add to that?
All right, we're gonna leave it right
there as we continue to move on to our
next question. I'm sorry, brother. I'm
sorry. The Lord said these are the
aisles of the Gentiles.
So all that, China, Japan, all are east
and they are the aisles of the Gentiles.
All of Europe. All of it.
That's all I got. I apologize.
All right, Sister Deborah, go ahead.
Yes. Alina Lonely asks, "Is it okay to
light incense or anoint family members
with oil if you're a female?" All right.
If you're a female, can you light
incense and anoint family members with
oil? Just call them.
No, you cannot go to James 5 and read
verse 14.
Okay. James 5 and14 says, "Is any sick
among you? Let him call for the elders
of the church and let them pray over
him, anointing him with oil in the name
of the Lord."
That's what you do.
Woman cannot. That's all I have to say.
All right, we'll leave it right there as
we continue. Believe we're going into a
new territory now. Uh, yes, we are now
into tonight's Q&A for Wednesday, June
the 11th, 2025.
Most love asks,
"Does everyone have a time to die?"
Someone said God does not have a time
for everyone to die and that we die
through carelessness.
Well, we know you can definitely die
through uh carelessness. No doubt about
that. But um let's open this question up
to the panel
because I know that scripture say it's a
time for everything. Brother Dre,
he said the panel.
Yes, sir. Three command and and read
what the Lord say about honoring your
mother and your father.
The commandments say correct. Exodus 20
and 12 says, "Honor thy father and thy
mother, that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee." Now, right there, that tells the
whole story. If you don't honor your
father and your mother, then your days
can be shortened. But if you do honor
your father and your mother, your days
could be long upon the earth. That mean
that you uh uh can decide how long you
going to be on this earth.
God don't have no set time or you I'm
going to let this guy live 15 years and
he going to die. This guy going to live
40 years and he going to die. No, you
can die by your own hand by misbehaving.
That's why I said if you honor your
mother and your father, your days could
would be long on this earth. If you
don't, it could be short.
That's all I have to say.
Dre, did you have something? No, that's
good.
You're right.
Okay, we'll leave it right there as we
move on to our next question, which is
also open to the panel. Uh, yes. Be
alert as in Revelations 19 verse 13. Is
Jesus clothing red with blood? because
he destroyed Edom first by himself.
Why don't we go to Revelation 19?
Okay, and read that verse 13. And they
want to know if that scripture is
pertaining to Edom only. Go ahead,
brother Jay.
And he was clothed with a vesture dipped
in blood and his name is called the word
of God.
Open to the path.
Okay, let's go to Isaiah the 34th
chapter and start reading verse one.
Okay,
34.
Is it Ezekiel 34? Isaiah 63.
Well, that's Isaiah 63 is is one. Yeah.
I want Ezekiel 34 first and then we go
to Isaiah 63. Yes, sir. Okay. Uh Isaiah
34 and1 says, "Come near ye nations to
hear, and hearken ye people. Let the
earth hear and all that is therein, the
world, and all things that come forth of
it." For the indignation of the Lord is
upon all nations, and his f and his fury
upon all their armies. He utterly
destroyed them, and he delivered them to
the slaughter. Yes, sir.
Go ahead. Their slain also shall be cast
out, and their stink shall come up out
of their carcasses, and the mountain
shall be melted with their blood.
Just letting you know it's going to be a
lot of blood. Now you go in Isaiah 63.
Okay.
Verse one.
Who is this that cometh from Edom with
dyed garments from Bozro?
This that is glorious in his apparel,
traveling in the greatness of his
strength. I speak in righteousness
mighty to save.
Wherefore art thou red in thy in thine
apparel, and thy garments like him that
treadth in the wine fat? I have treaded
I have trotten the wine press alone. And
of the people there was none with me.
For I will tread them in mine anger and
trample them in my fury. and their blood
shall be sprinkled upon my garments and
I will stain all my raignment.
So that's what the red on his garments
is not only just from Esauh
is also from the whole world. Yeah.
Because the Lord going to kill a lot of
people and say his vessels shall be
dipped in blood
and everybody else because remember this
is going to be the war of Armageddon. It
tells you in Jeremiah 25
that the slain of the Lord going to be
from one end of the earth to the other.
110th chapter Psalm that he going to
fill the places with dead bodies.
Sure. The garments on it the red uh
garments dipped in the uh uh uh
that was red represent the killing of a
lot of people, not just Esau.
Right.
Yeah. Joel 3 chapter Joel 3 says
multitude multitudes in the valley of
decision.
Uhhuh.
In Revelation the blood the horse is
brow.
Yeah. So serve God so you can stay out
the way.
And in both
in in Isaiah 63 and4 it says for the day
of the Lord's vengeance is in my heart
and the year of my redeemed has come.
And in Isaiah 34 and 8 it says for it is
the day of the Lord's vengeance and the
year of recompenses for the controversy
of Zion. So Lord is coming to deal with
all.
Yeah.
Yeah. So, uh can we read Revelations? Uh
he gives Revelations 19 verse3.
Okay.
It says, "And he was clothed with a
vesture dipped in blood, and his name is
called the Word of God."
Yeah. From Kenneth.
Yeah.
And the word of God, that's Jesus. Like
I say in St. John the first chapter, in
the beginning was the word. The word was
with God and the word was God.
Yeah. All things him.
He was in the world and the world knew
him not.
Yeah.
And like he like we said already, his
garments going to be stained with blood.
Blood of men.
Yeah.
Yeah. And right with his comment, he
wants to know was it because he
destroyed Edom first by himself?
He didn't say he destroyed Edom. He said
he come from Edom,
right? He had killed a whole lot of
people. People ain't going to be Edom
ain't going to be the first one that he
kill. Remember when he come, it's going
to be the war of Armageddon. That is
east and west.
He told you in the book of over he gonna
hurt them.
But he coming from Edom.
Yeah.
Ain't going to be the first to kill.
First he going to start with is the
Europeans. East and Western Europe. Mhm.
But the Lord say if you don't cut it
short,
but for
he going to cut it short. He going to
come in the war of Armageddon is when
the Lord's going to take on Easter. In
fact,
the 19th chapter of Revelation and read
verse 19. Okay. Revelation 19 and verse
19 says, "And I saw the beast and the
kings of the earth and their armies
gathered together to make war against
him that sat on the horse and against
his army." Now, how many kings of the
earth was it?
All of and their kings of the ar and
their armies. Yes. So, it was all of
kings of the earth.
So, so, so that just don't include Edom.
Yeah, that just don't single out Edom
and the beast and the king and the kings
of the earth and the forest prophet, all
those talking about Europeans. Edom is
going to be among them because
everybody's going to be among them.
Yeah.
Yeah. Zachchariah says is he his feet
going to hit the Mount of Olives and he
gonna bring all them people to the uh
valley of Migadoo.
All the all armies. Yeah. All armies.
That's why it's called of Armageddon
because it going to take place in the
valley of Migadoo.
Yep. So, yep. That's it. So, serve God
that you may escape his wrath. All
right. We hope that that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
Uh, moving on. Brit Brat has two
questions. The first one is those who
kill others with the same reason as Cain
and Judas did, can they be saved?
All right.
Open.
Ecclesiastes what book?
Ninth chapter
rather be a a a
living dog than a dead lion.
Ecclesiastes chapter 9. Yeah.
Verse four.
It says, "For to him that is joined to
all the living there is hope. For a
living dog is better than a dead lion.
So now as long as you are living, there
is hope. No matter what you have done,
the only crime sin you won't be forgiven
of. And the Bible said that is is when
you sin against the Holy Ghost. And that
is when you hold the truth in God and
unrighteousness which Roman which is in
Romans the first chapter starting verse
sure
then against the Holy Ghost that's when
you hold the truth and unrighteousness
you're teaching people wrong and you
know you're teaching people wrong but as
far as somebody you can repent from
anything.
Okay. Do you want me to read Romans
1:18?
Go ahead. For the wrath of God is
revealed from heaven against all
ungodliness and unrighteousness of men
who hold the truth in unrighteousness.
Now, if you hold the truth as
unrighteous, that mean you know it.
Isn't that correct? Yes, sir. Correct.
Because because that which may be known
of God is manifest in them. For God has
showed it unto them.
For the invisible things of him from the
creation of the world are clearly seen,
being understood by the things that are
made, even his eternal power and
godhead, so that they are are without
excuse.
So now the whole thing is those are the
that's the only sin that you cannot but
won't be forgiven. That's when you sin
against the Holy Ghost. It's all that
simple.
All right. And and Hebrews the 10th
chapter, if you sin willfully after he
after you have uh receive the knowledge
of the truth, right? Only thing you have
to look for is make a fly.
As long as you can be changed,
you can be saved.
All right. Hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on. Yes.
In her second question,
uh she states, "Can the life shall go
for life rule be exercised?"
She gives um a couple of of scriptures.
Deuteronomy 19 verse 21,
Exodus 21
verse 23
and Ecclesiastes
3:3.
And the question again is
can the life shall go for life rule be
exercised?
not understanding but maybe you brothers
have some understanding of that
question.
Yeah. Um actually a scripture or two
over beyond our requirement but let's go
to Deuteronomy 19. Please keep them to
two scripts. Let's go to Deuteronomy 19
and pick it up at verse 21
and let's put some interpretation on
that. Okay. And if the life of life is
still good today,
Deborah,
um
I don't know. Uh the the way she has it
is can the life
shall go for life rule be exercised? So
it looks like brother Julius what she's
saying here when we read that
Deuteronomy 19 and 20 she want to know
is it still a life for life and an eye
for an eye and tooth for tooth and all
that but let's read that verse brother
James and then we'll open up to the pal
okay and thine eye shall not pity but
life shall go for life eye for eye tooth
for tooth hand for hand foot for foot
open to the panel for that.
Well, when the Lord brought man across
the flood,
he he broke the covenant with the
animals
and uh he said that everybody's
life will be required at the hand of the
animals and also at the hand of men.
I think this I think this in Genesis the
ninth chapter.
Okay.
Yes. Yes, that is uh Genesis 9 uh versus
let's see uh verse five.
It says,
it says, "And surely your blood of your
lives will I require at the hand of
every beast will I require it, and at
the hand of man, and at the hand of
every man's brother will I require the
life of man."
What he's telling you there is, you
know, quite naturally, beast will kill
you. But when a man break the law or do
something
against the law, murder somebody, then
that's what you have law. They take him
to court, they try, they convict him,
and then uh uh if they call if uh and
some of them get life, and some of them
are executed. Yeah. But the Lord said
it's going to be required at the hand of
beast and man's blood going to be
required at the hand of man. In other
words, you do something wrong, the Lord
ain't going to shoot no lightning out of
heaven, kill you. He going to live the
law. He going to let you fall in the law
of man.
Right?
So you break a law, you suffer the
consequences. There ain't nothing
changed.
Yeah.
Can can we read um the Romans 13
where it says, "Let every soul be
subject unto the higher powers that the
Lord set up."
Go ahead. Okay. Get there.
And Romans Romans 13. Yeah. Read one
through four. Okay. It says, "Let every
soul be subject unto the higher powers,
for there is no power but of God. The
powers that be are ordained of God.
Whosoever therefore resisteth the power
resisteth the ordinance of God, and they
that resist shall receive to themselves
damnation.
For the rule, for rulers are not a
terror to good works, but to evil. Wilt
thou then not be afraid of the power. Do
that which is good, and thou shalt have
praise of the same?
For he is the minister of God to thee
for good. But if thou do that which is
evil, be afraid, for he beareth not the
sword in vain. For he is the minister of
God, a revenger to execute wrath upon
him that doeth evil.
Now, the Lord ordained that in Genesis
the 9th chapter, sir. Nothing has
changed.
And brother Cornell, I think you were
going to say something, but you're on
mute.
Yeah. Let's let's uh go into that. Well,
she got another script here which is
basically kind of saying what it said in
Deuteronomy 19, but Exodus 21 and then
one verse 23 is still talking about thou
giving that life for life. Go ahead.
If men strive and hurt a woman with
child so that her Uhuh. Exodus, you you
in Exodus 21. Yes. And verse 23. Okay.
Sorry about that. And if any mischief
follow, then thou shalt give life for
life.
I for
there's no need to answer the same
question over and over again. The
question has been answered. Okay.
And I'm not sure what he cla. But if
it's on the same thing, then we're going
to keep moving right on along. All
right. Uh the next question is from be
alert. and be alert as may you
chronically listen to the order of
events that Jesus will do when he
returns. Teach, fight, building of the
new temple, the second recovery of
Israel.
It's a whole lot into that question. Uh,
what you say, guest caller?
I didn't understand the question. Right?
Because he's just saying, uh, may you,
he says, may you, or can you chronically
listen to the order of events that Jesus
will do when he returns? Teach, fight,
building of the new temple, the second
recovery of Israel. So, can you listen
to the order of events?
Eventually,
eventually you're going to have a great
tribulation. After that, the Lord's
going to come after three and a half
years and take down the beast and false
prophet. Then the Lord is going to go
into the wilderness. Ezekiel the 20th
chapter tell you that. And while these
in the wilderness uh uh uh for the last
for three and a half years that's the
last half of this weekel
and those in the first resurrection
going to be building the temple
and after three and a half years of
teaching then he going to take Israel in
the land after he have purged out the
rebels and brought the rest of them into
the bond of the covenant.
That's the way.
Yeah.
Yeah. And that's a snippet as to what's
to come.
All right. We're going to leave it there
and move on to our our next question.
Yeah. Next question from uh Tanya
or Tanya Ligins asks for you to explain
Romans 14 verse1 17.
Uh she says, "I'm trying to make someone
understand that it doesn't mean you can
eat anything."
Romans 14 verse1 17.
All right, let's open this up also to
the panel. For the kingdom of God is not
meat and drink. Brother James, go right
ahead. For the kingdom of God is not
meat and drink, but righteousness and
peace and joy in the Holy Ghost.
All right. For the kingdom of God is not
meat and drink, but righteousness and
peace and joy in the Holy Ghost. Well,
we know it can't be even bread alone
because Jesus said himself that man
don't live by bread alone, but by every
word that proceedth out of the mouth of
the Lord does man live.
Can can we bag up and read verse one and
two in that same chapter?
Okay. All right. Go ahead. Him that is
weak in the faith receive ye but not to
doubtful disputations.
Go ahead. For one believeth that he may
eat all things, another who is weak
eateth herbs. So you got one that eats
according to the dietary law and another
one just eating herbs, vegetables.
say, "Receive ye him, but not to
doubtful disputations."
This is not talking about eating unclean
animals. Uh, eating all kind of unclean
animals. Nowhere in the Bible do you
read about any of the apostles, the
prophets, none of them eating unclean
animals. No, it's not in there.
Peter said, "I have never eaten anything
common unclean." At the coming of the
Lord, the Lord is going to deal with
those eating unclean animals.
Yeah. Leviticus 11,
it is separated when the word of God
tells you in Timothy it is sanctified by
the word of God and truth. Nothing to be
refused if it be received with
thanksgiving. For it is sanctified by
the word of God and prayer. It is
separated by the word of God. When did
he separate it? In Leviticus 11,
the clean from the unclean.
And then the kingdom of God is
righteousness.
What is that? The keeping of the
commandments from Genesis to Revelation.
Just keep the commandments.
And you read
one thing. Leviticus 20 and read verse
23. Okay. Leviticus 20 23.
Leviticus Leviticus 20 and verse 23
says,
"And ye shall not walk in the manners of
the nation which I cast out before."
Keep reading. Oh, 21 and 23.
Keep reading.
Okay. Um
verse 20 and 23
says, "And ye shall not walk in the
manners of the nation which I cast out
before you, for they committed all these
things, and therefore I abhored them."
Go ahead. But but I but I have said unto
you, ye shall inherit the land, and I
will give it unto you to possess it, a
land that flowth with milk and honey. I
am the Lord your God, which have
separated you from other people.
Go ahead. Ye shall therefore put
difference between clean beasts and
unclean, and between unclean fowls and
clean. And ye shall not make your souls
abominable by beast, or by foul, or by
any manner of living thing that creepeth
on the ground, which I have separated
from you as unclean.
Which who have separated it? The Lord.
Which I have separated.
So when you talking about if one believe
this and another believe another, that
don't mean nothing. It is what the Lord
have separated. That's right. So do the
Lord change? Let's go into Hebrews 13.
We're going to read one verse. Verse 18.
Verse 8.
Hebrews 13 and verse 8.
Mhm. Jesus Christ the same yesterday and
today and forever.
So now if he has separated the beast,
the clean from the unclean cuz he didn't
want you to eat him and he don't change
then where is there room for anybody
anything to change? No room. Exactly.
In case you don't know who it was that
was back there with Moses them, go to
first Corinthian the 10th chapter and
start reading at verse one. Okay. 1
Corinthians 10
and verse 1 says, "Moreover, brethren, I
would not that ye should be ignorant how
that all our fathers were under the
cloud, and all passed through the sea,
and were all baptized unto Moses in the
cloud and into the sea, and did eat did
all eat the same spiritual meat, and did
all drink the same spiritual drink? For
they drank of that spiritual rock that
followed them. And that rock was Christ.
Yep. Rock was who? Was Christ. That mean
he brought he gave the dietary law,
didn't it? Yes, sir. That mean he the
one said, "I want you to separate the
clean from the unclean which I have
separated from you." Ain't that what he
said? Yes.
And then he said in Hebrews uh uh 13:8,
Jesus Christ the same yesterday, today,
and forever. Why is there any room for
you to change? None. No matter what
Paul's right look like.
But Peter told you, we have a most sure
word of prophecy. Yes, sir.
Just like uh
brother Dre said in Isaiah 66, he going
to consume pig eaters.
That's all I have to say. Yeah. So, hey,
let's get it together, people. Come on.
All right, sister Deborah. Moving on to
our next question. Next question.
Pearlene R says, "Please help me
understand Deuteronomy 7:es
1-4.
Who are these nations in these times?"
Deuteronomy 7
1-4.
Who are these nations in this time
comingites and gerbishites and so forth,
brother James? But go ahead, read it.
Let's open it up to the panel, brother.
when the Lord thy God shall bring thee
into the land whether thou goest to
possess it, and hast cast out many
nations before thee, the Hittites, and
the Gegosites, and the Amorites, and the
Canaanites, and the Perizzites, and the
Hivites, and the Jebusites, seven
nations greater, and mightier than thou.
And when the Lord thy God shall deliver
them before thee, thou shalt smite them,
and utterly destroy them. Thou shalt
make no covenant with them, nor show
mercy unto them. Neither shalt thou make
marriages with them. Thy daughters thou
shalt not give unto the to his son, nor
his daughters shall thou take unto thy
son. For they will turn away thy son
from following me, that they may serve
other gods. So will the anger of the
Lord be kindled against you and destroy
thee suddenly.
All right. So who are these modern time
people? I think you mentioned something
earlier, brother Julius. The Hittites
and Amorites and Canaanites and so
forth. Go to Genesis chapter 10. Okay.
Pick it up at verse 6.
Okay. It says, "And the sons of Ham,
Kush and Misra, and Foot and Canaan." So
now, Kush, your Ethiopians,
Misraim,
uh, your ancient Egyptians,
put your Libyans and Canaan, took the
land from the Canaanites. These are the
children of Ham, Hammites, and their
subdivisions. Skip down, skip down to
verse 13.
and Misraam begat Luden and Anamim and
Lehim
and Nefam.
Verse 15.
And Canaan begat Sidon his firstborn in
He. Uhhuh. And the Jebusite and the
Amorite. There's the Jebusites. Children
of Canaan. There's your Jebusite. Go
ahead. And the Amorite. Yep. And the
Gegosite. And the Gegosites. and the
other people that come out of the
children of Canaan. So these are some of
your African peoples today.
All right, hope that answered your
question there as we continue to move on
with a time check. Yes, the time is
8:51.
MJ asks, "What does it mean to be ye
angry and sin not in Ephesians 4 verse
26?
Does it mean that people can disrespect
and say whatever they want to you?" And
again is Ephesians 4 verse 26. What does
it mean to be angry and sin not?
All right, why don't we go there,
Brother James? And yeah, people entitled
to say pretty much what they want to say
to you, but uh you have to always
maintain your temperance and your
self-control.
But just like you say, be angry and when
the sun go down, you finished with that
cuz that is a new day getting ready to
kick in, right? Get get there, my
brother. Go ahead. Be ye angry and sin
not. Let not the sun go down upon your
wrath.
Now, what is sin? Somebody go and read
what sin is. First John 3:4.
First John 3 and 4. It says
1 John 3:4 says, "Whosoever committeth
sin transgresseth also the law, for sin
is the transgression of the law."
So don't let nobody make you so angry
until you break one of God's
commandments. Right.
That's all it mean.
Yeah.
All right. Check it out. We'll leave it
right there as we move on as we are
coming down to our last couple of
questions. Go right ahead. Yes. Kim Noel
asks in Acts 12 verse4
in the KJV,
is the word Easter a mistransation?
Should it be Passover? Because in other
versions of the Bible, it does say
Passover.
Yep, indeed. It should be Passover. And
you with the King James? That is an
excellent choice. Go ahead, read it,
brother James. Let's open that up to the
panel.
And when he had apprehended him, he put
him in prison and delivered him to four
courtians
of soldiers to keep him, intending after
Easter to bring him forth to the people.
Yeah, that's a gentile. That's a gentile
translation because remember no book
Acts and all of them was written by
Hebrews
and Hebrews wouldn't use no word like
Easter. So somebody during the
translation put Easter there in place of
Passover
and that somebody had one of maybe the
scholars in Cambridge uh uh uh uh what's
his other university in England? Oxford,
right? One of them Gentiles. Oh,
Passover. That's all that's our Easter.
And he wrote Easter. I knew it had to be
that way cuz they know Hebrew was going
to write. And Acts was written by a
recorder.
You know, a scribe. Israel had scribes.
Ain't no scribes going to use the
Gentile term Easter.
Was only in there one time. And that's a
typo, right?
I don't think typo
it's a it's a mistransation.
Yeah. But with some knowledge you know
what word should be there.
Correct. And that is Passover. Okay.
As we move on to our next question. Next
question. Orlando David uh Davey asks is
uh asks who is David referring to in
Psalms 55
13 and 14. Who is David referring to?
13 and 14.
Right. Why don't we go there, brother
James?
And this is where the
the son was talking about his father
here. Go ahead. But let's read it. But
it was pick it up. Hey, James, pick it
up at verse 12. Let's read down into it
because it says he's talking about the
godhead here. Go ahead. For it was not
an enemy that reproached me. Then I
could have borne it. Neither was it he
that hated me that did magnify himself
against me. Then I would have hid myself
from him. But it was thou a man mine
equal, my God and mine acquaintance.
We took sweet counsel together and
walked into the house of God in company.
And that question again, Deborah,
who is David referring to in Psalms 55
verses 13 and 14? Jesus
by the mouth of David.
Yeah. He let the fun to the father uh uh
uh uh he's the one that made his soul an
offering for sin. That's why it said if
it was the enemy, you could have hid
from him. But if it's you one that's my
my equal.
That's what it say. Isn't that correct?
Yes, sir.
Go to Isaiah the 56th chapter
and uh uh we're going to start we going
to start at verse one and just going to
show you Isaiah 56 and1.
Okay. Thus sayeth the Lord, keep ye
judgment and do justice, for my
salvation is near to come, and my
righteousness to be revealed.
Blessed is the man that doeth this, and
the son of man that layeth hold on it,
that keepeth the 53. Oh, Isaiah 53.
Okay. Uhhuh.
It says
53 and one. Correct.
Right. Then we going to skip. Okay. Who
hath believed our report? And to whom is
the arm of the Lord revealed?
Go ahead. He shall grow up before him as
a tender plant, and as a root out of a
dry ground. He hath no form, nor
comeliness. And when we shall see him,
there is no beauty that we should desire
him. Go ahead. He is despised and
rejected of men, a man of sorrows, and
acquainted with grief. And we hid as it
if as it were our faces from him. He was
He was despised, and we esteemed him
not.
Surely he hath borne our griefs, and
carried our sorrows. Yet we did esteem
him stricken, smitten of God, and
afflicted.
But he was
Wow. Ah, God. Mhm. Smitten of God and
afflicted.
Who is But he was wounded for our
transgressions. He was bruised for our
iniquities. The chastisement of our
peace was upon him, and with his stripes
we are healed. Uh-huh. Skip down to
verse 10. Okay. Yet it pleased the Lord
to bruise him. He has put him to grief.
When thou shalt make his soul an
offering for sin, he shall see his seed.
He shall prolong his days, and the
pleasure of the Lord shall prosper in
his hand.
Who who is the one that brewed the Lord?
The father.
And he also said, "One that's mine
equal." Didn't he say that? Yes.
Philippians.
Second,
it's 2 and5. Yes, it says, "Let this
mind be in you which was also in Christ
Jesus."
Six, uh, who being in the form of God,
thought it not robbery to be equal with
God. Man, my equal. So, that's that's
right. So, that covers it all, didn't
it? man. His is the one that that that
had him crucified for the sins of the
people. That's why he said if it was an
enemy, he could have hid from it. So
David is talking about Jesus and what
the father did to him.
The same two. So they took sweet counsel
together. That's the answer to that.
Yep. All right. Sister Deborah, our time
check. Yes. The time is 9:00.
All right, nine o'clock. So, we want to
say that we have ran out of time and we
want to thank everybody from all around
the world who tuned in and ask those
questions. And we took joy in answering
those questions for you. We like to say
if you submitted a question and we have
a chance to get to it, please don't
resubmit it. Sister Deborah, take it,
put it in rotation, and we will deal
with it next week at the same day, same
time. So until we all come together
again, be safe, be blessed, stay prayed
up as brother James closes us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name, thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven. Give us this day our daily
bread. And forgive us our debts as we
forgive our debtors. And lead us not
into temptation, but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever. in Jesus
name we